<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kuruksastra 19</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="cookie_shared">COOKIE_SHARED_PREF</string>
    <string name="cookie_key">COOKIE_KEY</string>

    <string name="shared_pref">SHARED_PREF</string>
    <string name="login_or_not">LOGIN_OR_NOT</string>
    <string name="login_register_action">FROM_LOGIN_OR_REGISTER</string>
    <string name="is_qr_saved">IS_QR_SAVED</string>

    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="logout">Log out</string>
    <string name="kuruksastra_19">Kuruksastra\'19</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="ambassador_id">Ambassador ID</string>
    <string name="college_name">College Name</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="otp">OTP</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="sent_to_email">OTP is sent to email</string>


    <!--clusters-->
    <string-array name="cluster_list">
        <item>FlagShip Event</item>
        <item>Arts</item>
        <item>Dramatics</item>
        <item>English Lits</item>
        <item>Hindi Lits</item>
        <item>SASTRA Eastern Dance Team</item>
        <item>SASTRA Western Dance Team</item>
        <item>Telugu Lits</item>
        <item>SASTRA FotoHub</item>
        <item>சாஸ்த்ரா தமிழ்ச் சங்கம்</item>
        <item>SASTRA Music Team</item>
        <item>300 DPI</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- mr and mrs kiruk-->
    <string-array name="kuruk_event_list">
        <item>Mr. &amp; Ms. Kuruksastra</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--mr and mrs kiruk desc-->
    <string-array name="kuruk_desc_list">
        <item>Take the stage and showcase your talent for a shot at the
prestigious mr. and ms. titles</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- mr and mrs kiruk rules-->
    <string-array name="kuruk_rules_list">
        <item>• No profanity or vulgarity will be tolerated.\n
• Individual event.\n
• first round will be a talent showcase. participants will have to bring
their own props.\n
• further rounds will be impromptu.\n
• participants will be judged based on their creativity and spontaneity.\n
• judges decision will be final</item>


    </string-array>


    <!--art events list -->
    <string-array name="arts_list">
        <item>Monochrome - Pencil Sketching</item>
        <item>Character Design</item>
        <item>Paper Dressing</item>
        <item>Face painting</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- art events desc-->
    <string-array name="arts_desc_list">
        <item>Monochrome’ is a basic pencil sketching event where
        participants will have to draw and shade on the given topic
        within stipulated time.</item>

        <item>Participants have to design a new character or a new skin for
a character of their choice from any game or book or movie.</item>

        <item>Newspapers: cut them, stick them, or fold them, and finally
make them serve the purpose, and the dress will speak for
itself!</item>

        <item>A gentle stroke of the brush, A tinge of glitter and an
overflowing imagination</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- art events rules-->
    <string-array name="arts_rules_list">
        <item>• Use of materials other than the ones provided will lead to disqualification\n
• Topics will be given on spot\n
• Judges decision is final\n
• Individual event\n
• Use of external references is not allowed</item>

        <item>• Use of materials other than the ones provided will lead to disqualification\n
• Judges decision is final\n
• Individual event\n
• Use of external references is not allowed</item>

        <item>• Use of materials other than the ones provided will lead to disqualification\n
• Topics will be given on spot\n
• Judges decision is final\n
• Maximum of 4 people per team (Minimum 2)\n
• Use of external references is not allowed</item>

        <item>• 2 per team (1 painter and 1 to be painted upon)\n
• Use of materials other than the ones provided will lead to disqualification\n
• Topics will be given on spot\n
• Judges decision is final\n
• Use of external references is not allowed</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- dramatics event list-->
    <string-array name="dramatic_list">
        <item>Improv</item>
        <item>MonoAct</item>
        <item>One Act Play</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- dramatics events desc-->
    <string-array name="dramatics_desc_list">
        <item>With only wit by your side, are you ready to test your acting chops? Do you have
what it takes to tackle any situation thrown at you? Sharpen your wits and get
ready to think like lightning as you take on our improv event!</item>

        <item>One stage. One person. All lights on you. Do you have what it takes to steal the show?</item>

        <item>Welcome to The Studio’s flagship event! One of Kuruksastra’s biggest draws, the One Act Play is your chance to showcase your talent and cast a
spell on your audience with the magic of theatre.</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- dramatic events rules-->
    <string-array name="dramatics_rules_list">
        <item>• Exactly 4 participants in a team.\n
• There are multiple elimination rounds.\n
• Event specifics will be revealed on the spot (this is improv, after all.)\n
• Vulgarity and profanity are strictly prohibited.\n
• Judges’ decision is final and binding.\n
• No use of lights and sounds allowed.</item>

        <item>• Time limit is 6 to 8 minutes. Please adhere to it.\n
• The script can be a monologue or a monoact.\n
• Vulgarity and profanity are strictly prohibited.\n
• Please bring your own props and costume. You will be provided tables and chairs if
required.\n
• Original scripts carry brownie points.\n
• Judges’ decision is final and binding.</item>

        <item>• Time limit is 30 to 45 minutes, empty stage to empty stage. Please adhere to it.\n
• Vulgarity and profanity are strictly prohibited.\n
• No. of participants per team: 10 (+2 crew)\n
• Please submit your scripts by 11.59 pm, March 15 2019 to dramatics.studio@gmail.com\n
• Please bring your own props and costume. You will be provided tables and chairs if required. Directors are
requested to notify us of your requirements before March 18.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- english lits events list-->
    <string-array name="english_lits_list">
        <item>What\'s The Good Word?</item>
        <item>CrossWord</item>
        <item>Scrabble</item>
        <item>Dumb Charades</item>
        <item>PotPurri</item>
        <item>Just A Minute(JAM)</item>
        <item>Extempore</item>
        <item>Debate</item>
        <item>The Gen Quiz</item>
        <item>Bizspent Quiz</item>
        <item>The Fandom Quiz</item>
        <item>India Quiz</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--english lits events desc-->
    <string-array name="english_lits_desc_list">
        <item>Think you are punny? Have a way with words? Can find the good word no
matter how badly we present it to you? Then head right over as we test your
brain with a plethora of fun word games that will leave you wondering...
what’s the good word?”</item>

        <item>Grid? Check! CLues? Check!
What more are you waiting for?
Break the clue, twist it, turn it on its head! Do all it takes to decode the
clues and become the Cryptic master!</item>

        <item>A nostalgic board game which gets more competitive than our friendly
family matches. Scrabble to put your best tiles forward and Bingo!
You win!</item>

        <item>Actions speak louder than words. Show us your team’s chemistry by
battling it out with actions.</item>

        <item>A combination of all the events that happen at ELS. Be prepared to face any
challenge that’s thrown at you.</item>

        <item>The signature event of ELS. One minute to object. One minute to keep
talking. One minute to rule them all.</item>

        <item>Practice makes perfect, but perfect is boring. Make it up as you go!</item>

        <item>Do you like to argue relentlessly to get your point across? Engage in a
war of words at ELS’s own debate</item>

        <item>A Quiz about anything and everything under the sun including it. If you think
you know the answer to every question, this quiz is just the thing for you</item>

        <item>Find the Sportstar more appealing than The Hindu? Love a Buffet? By
combining the best of both worlds, we’ll give you more than 13 Reasons
Why you should be here.</item>

        <item>One can never have enough questions, but then winter is coming, so you have
only one shot to rule them all!
May the odds be in your favour!</item>

        <item>Think you can bombard us with the knowledge of the Great Indian
Subcontinent?
Ready your arms as you battle through the KurukSastra India Quiz at
ELS</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--english lits events rules-->
    <string-array name="english_lits_rules_list">
        <item>• Teams of 2</item>

        <item>• Teams of 2\n
• Standard Cryptic Crossword rules apply</item>

        <item>• Teams of 2\n
• Official CSW15 Dictionary words only</item>

        <item>• Teams of 3 only\n
• No cross-reference</item>

        <item>• Teams of 4 only\n
• No-cross reference</item>

        <item>• Individual event</item>

        <item>• Individual Event\n
• Prelims will consist of Shipwreck/ Block and Tackle/ Spin a yarn</item>

        <item>• One goes FOR (Sp time: 4 mins), one goes Against (Sp time: 4 mins). Total 8 mins\n
• Only for the prelims, the third person will be given a topic 15 mins before his team goes
up and he will have to debate either for/against the motion with all the resources at
hand! (Impromptu debate). Speaking time includes rebuttal time too\n
• Prelims will be held during the week (Internal Participants only). External
participants can contact the event organisers to book a slot.</item>

        <item>• Teams of 3\n
• Prelims and finals</item>

        <item>• Teams of 3\n
• Will contain elements of Biz with emphasis on Sports and Ent
portions of the quiz\n
• Prelims and Finals</item>

        <item>• Teams of 3\n
• One shot quiz\n
• Fandoms not limited to HP, LoTR, ASoIaF</item>

        <item>• Teams of 2\n
• Prelims and Finals</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- hindi lits event list-->
    <string-array name="hindi_lits_list">
        <item>Antakshri - Geet gata chal</item>
        <item>Dramebaaz -Hindi Drama</item>
        <item>India Quiz- Mahaan Bharat</item>
        <item>Extempore – bol vachan</item>
        <item>Dumbc- isharon isharon me</item>
        <item>Debate – vaad vivaad</item>
        <item>Fun Events -matargasti</item>
        <item>Bhasha Paribhasha ( Creative writing)</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- hindi lits desc list-->
    <string-array name="hindi_lits_desc_list">
        <item>Baithe baithe kya karein? Karna hai kuch kaam, shuru karein antakshri, leke unmaad
ka naam. Presenting the ageless “ desi” game of Antakshri, and here’s serving it with
a twist to spice it up. If you’re mad about Bollywood, We’ve got just the event for you.
From bathroom artists to stage performers, anyone who has a song for every occasion
is invited. So shed your inhibitions, refresh your memory and grab your claim to fame at
Unmaad.</item>

        <item>Are you an entertainer? Do you wish to taste the glory of a “dramebaaz”. Unmaad presents
“TAMASHA” – a platform to show us the comedian, the actor, the performer inside you. Sign
up and release that energy trusting inside you. Get crowned as the biggest nautanki and
drama queens</item>

        <item>Do you know about our incredible India? Do you know about its past, present and future?
If the answer is yes, you have what it takes to call yourself “MAHAN BHARTIYA”.</item>

        <item>In the candor inculcating… in the humor of a smile. In the lap of all tomorrow’s …we will
sit and talk awhile… few minutes is what you get.. to speak what you set..</item>

        <item>The sound of silence could never have felt this good. What with flailing hands and
frantic gestures. We assure you a riot of fun in this wildly popular battle. Bina kuch bol
ke bole to “BABU SAMJHO ISHARE”</item>

        <item>Charcha aadhunik vishiyon par aur apni tippani pradhan kare… one simply needs clarity in
thought and arguments to ace this .. just Argue Away..</item>

        <item>Once you begin being mentally and physically strong, it is easier to go and on and on, and
sooner or later something dreadful happens, but still your heart asks for more, then
join us for the event called “dil mange more” and get what you wished for</item>

        <item>Open your mind and go with the flow</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- hindi lits rules list-->
    <string-array name="hindi_lits_rules_list">
        <item>• .At least the first verse of the song must be sung. If the singer does not remember it in
entirety, they cannot use the song.\n
• No song can be repeated again in the game.\n
• No half answer will be considered.\n
• Judges decision will be final.\n
• 2 participants per team</item>

        <item>• Vulgarity will not be entertained.\n
• Extra time for preparation will not be provided.\n
• Written script should not exceed the given time.\n
• It is not allowed to use the same script (or a substantially similar script) in more than
one event at the same contest if there are any common cast members in both events.\n
• 5.If script is not original, credits for the same should be awarded.\n
        Participants: Maximum 9\n Time Limit: 20 Mins</item>

        <item>• Only team maximum of two entries are eligible (individual entry is accepted).\n
• A team shall consist of max two persons.\n
• The decision of the quiz-master will be final and will not be subjected to any change.\n
• The participants shall not be allowed to use mobile or other electronic instruments.\n
        Participants: 2</item>

        <item>• Hindi should be the language of communication.\n
• Time will be allotted to each contestant on spot.\n
• 3.The speech should include a brief introduction of the participant.\n
• A warning bell will be given at the end of 30 seconds.\n
• Decision of judges will be considered final.\n
• Discipline is of prime importance.\n
        Single Event</item>

        <item>• Air drawing is not permitted.\n
• In all rounds the person explaining the thing stands at least 2 feet away from partners.\n
• The acting person cannot speak anything from mouth, and cannot point to any object or a
person.\n
• Only one person comes in front to get a chit from the pool with a name on it.\n
• Judges decision will be final.\n
        Participants: 3</item>

        <item>• Abusive language is not allowed\n
• Vulgarity and profanity will not be allowed\n
• No revision of position of a team is permitted during the debate\n
• Judges decision will be final.\n
        Participants: 2</item>

        <item>• Decision of judges will be considered final\n
• Discipline is of prime importance\n
• Safety should be the first priority\n
• More rules and regulation regarding the event will be provided on spot\n
        Participants: 2</item>

        <item>• Have to submit a piece of writing portraying your inert creativity.\n
• The piece of writing needs to be associated with the pic/theme/video provided.\n
• It can be in any form poetry, short story, nano tale etc. Your writing shall be judged
against the writings of the same category.\n
• Profanity and vulgarity should be strictly avoided.\n
• Uncredited Plagiarism shall lead to disqualification.\n
        Individual Event</item>

    </string-array>


    <!-- eastern dance team event  list-->
    <string-array name="eastern_dance_list">
        <item>Nrithya Madhuryam- Classical Solo</item>
        <item>Choreo Night-Eastern Category(Theme/Non-Theme)</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--eastern dance desc list-->
    <string-array name="eastern_dance_desc_list">
        <item>Thanjavur, a city brimming with culture and heritage, is incomplete without the classical dance form. And what better way can there be to portray
the journey of dance from the past to the present, but ‘fusion’? The stage is set for you to present your combination of elegance and power
with Abhinaya and Nritta, fusing it with today’s rhythm. With the perfect blend of all the elements of classical dance, we bring to you this solo
classical event.</item>

        <item>Dance is a platform of expression. Powerful statements, intriguing stories or just graceful, rhythm catching beats can be what you perform on
this arena. Get your feet tapping and music playing to stun everyone with your vibrance. Get your crew out there and show the world what your
passionate lot has got!</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--eastern dance rules list-->
    <string-array name="eastern_dance_rules_list">
        <item>Date: 24th March, 2019\n
        Round1:\n
        • The participant is to perform a pure classical piece of his/her choice for a maximum
of 3 minutes.\n
• A prop of his/her choice is to be incorporated into the routine.\n
• Classical costume is mandatory.\n
• Any form of classical dance may be performed.\n
• Usage of powder, water, fire, or any other harmful prop will not be entertained.\n
        Round2:\n
        • A classical ‘Block and Tackle’. An exciting round where 2 emotions
will be given to the participant which has to be portrayed for the
music played on spot, putting their creativity and spontaneity to test</item>

        <item>Date: 23rd March,2019\n
        • The 1st round is a video prelims. Please send a Google drive link to thandavsdt@gmail.com by 15th March, 2019. Shortlisted teams will be informed by 16th March, 2019.
• All Eastern styles are allowed.
• Each team will be given a slot time of 8 min + 2 min for stage setup.
• Number of participants per team: 8 to 20 members with 2 back stage helpers.
• Only one team per category is allowed from each college.
• Powder, water, fire, sharp metal objects and other harmful props are not allowed.</item>


    </string-array>


    <!--western dance team event list -->
    <string-array name="western_dance_list">
        <item>Dual-Trio</item>
        <item>Solo Dance</item>
        <item>Choreo Night-Western Category</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- western dance desc list-->
    <string-array name="western_dance_desc_list">
        <item>If you are a lover of dance and yet find it challenging to go solo on stage, find a partner or two, sync your mind and moves to your favourite tunes
and grab this opportunity to showcase your treasure of talent, in the Dual-Trio dance event of Kuruksastra ‘19. Enchant us with your moves ,
overcome your hitches and create an identity with your partner(s)!</item>

        <item>Dance is music made visible to eyes. Have you got the flair to make this happen and dance the night out in parties? Here’s your chance to dance
to some of the most famous tunes, on the spot, right out of your head and turn it into the viewer’s delight! Participate in the solo dance event of
Kuruksastra ‘19, express yourself on stage as you would in your shower and spread the music to the world as a visual treat!</item>

        <item>Dancers are said to be God’s own athletes, sweating out hard just to experience the unison between the rhythm of the heartbeat, music and the feet. Are you one of those
crazy souls with a passionate crew? Then sweat out a bit more and show us your best routines. Set the stage and your heart alight with your most comfortable styles
of dance. Battle it out on the Choreo Night, against some of the best dance crews, showing the world why your crew is the best combo of God’s most favorite athletes!</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- western dance rules list-->
    <string-array name="western_dance_rules_list">
        <item>Date: 24th March,2019\n
        • 2 (or) 3 participants in a team.\n
• Time limit: 2 to 3 mins.\n
• Free to dance in more than 1 style.\n
• Participants should prepare their own music track, brought in a separate pen
drive containing only the track.\n
• Track to be submitted at the time of registration.\n
• Top 4 teams will qualify to the next round, a battle round.\n
• About battle round:\n The qualified teams will be made to adapt tune to songs of
any genre or language of 1 minute each, along with one surprise element which
will be revealed before the battle rounds. Vulgarity and profanity will not be
entertained at any cost.</item>

        <item>Date: 24th March,2019\n
        • DJ will play 3 different songs one after the other for 40 secs each and participants must dance for the same.\n
• No preparation time will be given (Adapt tune)\n
• Judgement will be based on spontaneity, adaptivity and how well you entertain the audience.\n
• Top 4 will qualify to the next round, a battle round.\n
• About battle round:\n The qualified participants will be made to adapt tune to songs of any genre or language of 1 minute each . Vulgarity and profanity will not be
entertained at any cost.</item>

        <item>Date: 23rd March,2019\n
        • 1st round is video prelims. Please send the YouTube link of your latest performance to
‘insidersastra@gmail.com’ on or before 20/03/2019.\n
• On 23th morning, there will be a 2nd round of prelims at starting at 9.30 AM. Teams that\n
arrive later will be disqualified. One person is required to wear the costume necessarily
for the prelims. The shortlisted teams will be allowed to perform on stage.\n
• Only Western styles are allowed.\n
• Each team is given a time slot of 7 minutes (6+1) including stage setup.\n
• Number of participants per team is 6 to 30 with a maximum of 2 back stage helpers.\n
• Only one team per category is allowed per college.\n
• Each team must submit a bonafide certificate for all the participants of the team signed
by the head of their institute and All team members should have their college ID cards.\n
• Fire, water and other properties that can damage the stage are strictly not allowed. No
indecency during performance.\n
• Copied routines will not be entertained and Judges decision is final.</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--telugu lits events list-->
    <string-array name="telugu_lits_list">
        <item>Oke Okka Chance</item>
        <item>Evadi Gola Vadidhi</item>
        <item>Pataku Pranam Pallavi Aithe</item>
        <item>Rangasthalam (Drama)</item>
        <item>Mr.Medhavi</item>
        <item>Kalam</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--telugu lits desc list-->
    <string-array name="telugu_lits_desc_list">
        <item>This is an acting event where your spontaneity plays a key role. You will be awarded for
your acting skills and spontaneity.</item>

        <item>It is a miscellaneous event having fun rounds and games.</item>

        <item>A music and movie quiz event where basic knowledge on songs and movies is enough to
participate. It contains 3 rounds.</item>

        <item>A drama event in which judgement is given based on acting and script selection.</item>

        <item>A general quiz event in which you need to be strong in general knowledge and current
affairs</item>

        <item>This event consists of Creative writing and poetry.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--telugu lits rules list-->
    <string-array name="telugu_lits_rules_list">
        <item>• Max 3 per team.\n
• Teams are selected on prelims basis.</item>

        <item>• Max 3 per team.\n
• Teams are selected on prelims basis.\n</item>

        <item>• Max 3 per team.\n
• Teams are selected on prelims basis.</item>

        <item>• Overall Drama length should not exceed 15mins.\n
• Teams are selected on prelims basis.\n
• Every team has to perform for 3-5 mins in Prelims.\n
• Team will be disqualified if there is any usage of unparliamentary language or Vulgarity</item>

        <item>• Max 3 per team.\n
• Teams are selected on prelims basis.</item>

        <item>• Hardcopy of your writings are to be submitted.\n
• External participants can E-mail a scanned copy of their writings.\n
• Topics and Last date of submission will be announced well in advance.\n
• Selection will be done based on how creatively you present the given topic</item>

    </string-array>

    <!--fotohub events list-->
    <string-array name="fotohub_list">
        <item>Salle De Cinema ‘19</item>
        <item>Bande-Annonce ‘19</item>
        <item>Photographia ‘19</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--fotohub desc list-->
    <string-array name="fotohub_desc_list">
        <item>Short film, just like feature films, is an individual art form.\n
The medium gives freedom to film-makers.\n
They can be more like a portrait, or a poem.</item>

        <item>When people listen to a song, they don’t just listen but also see visuals in their mind.\n
This is an opportunity to share those visuals with us.</item>

        <item>Photography is a medium that captures a specific event at a specific time in a specific
place.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--fotohub rules list-->
    <string-array name="fotohub_rules_list">
        <item>• The short films should be maximum of 15 minutes duration.\n
• Subtitles should be added for the short films.\n
• Avoid the use of profanity and vulgarity.\n
• Plagiarism will not be tolerated.\n
• The entries should be mailed to fotohub.sastra@gmail.com by March 16th.\n
• Judge’s decision is final.\n
• Registration fee of Rs.250 should be paid in order to\n
Participate in the competition.</item>

        <item>• Five films will be given, out of which the contestants can choose one film and create a
music video with footage from that film.\n
• Choice of song is left to the contestant.\n
• The song can be of any type and any language.\n
• The soundtracks from the given five films should not be used.\n
• The sounds or dialogues from the film can be used.\n
• Plagiarism will not be tolerated.\n
• The drive link of the entries should be mailed to
fotohub.sastra@gmail.com by March 19th</item>

        <item>• This is an online photography contest.\n
• Any device can be used to capture the photo.\n
• The contest has a total of 3 rounds, the first round is open while the following rounds are
theme specific.\n
• Each participant is expected to submit maximum of 3 photos for the first round and 2 photos
for the subsequent rounds.\n
• Participants will be shortlisted based on their entries from the first round and will be
notified of the theme for the subsequent rounds.\n
• The shortlisted participants are expected to capture the photo based on the
given theme in the stipulated time period.\n
• The photographs submitted must be the genuine, original work of the participant and void of
watermark of any sort.\n
• Basic post processing is allowed.\n
• Entries with offensive or inappropriate content or those which promote any specific brand
will be disqualified.\n
• The last date for submission for the open round is March 6th, any and all entries that are
submitted post the specified date will be disqualified.\n
• The participants are expected to mail their entries to fotohub.sastra@gmail.com</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- tamil sangam event list-->
    <string-array name="tamil_sangam_list">
        <item>சொற்போர் - DEBATE</item>
        <item>தமிழாட்டம் - TAMIL QUIZ</item>
        <item>எழுத்தோவியம் - CREATIVE WRITING</item>
        <item>கவிததோப்பு - POEM WRITING</item>
        <item>சினிமாப்பட்டி - CINE QUIZ</item>
        <item>மெட்டுப்போடு - SONGS QUIZ</item>
        <item>மௌனமொழி - DUMB CHARADES</item>
        <item>ஆல் இன் ஆல் அழகு ராஜா - POT POURRI</item>
        <item>நையாண்டி நாயகரக்ள் - KPY</item>
        <item>நவரசம் – DRAMA</item>
        <item>இராஜபாட் - Monoact</item>
        <item>வசனகாவியம் - SCRIPT SUBMISSION EVENT</item>
        <item>முகமொழி - MIME</item>
        <item>யாதுமாகி நின்றேன் – SOLO MIME</item>
        <item>கூத்துப்பட்டறை - STREET PLAY</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- tamil sangam desc list-->
    <string-array name="tamil_sangam_desc_list">
        <item>“போரக்களம் உங்கள் முன்னே
தீட்ட வேண் டியது வாள்முனையை அல்ல
உங்கள் நாமுனையை த் தான்
ஆம்! இது ஒரு சொற்போரக்களம்..!”</item>

        <item>“இலக்கியங்கள் இயலாக இலக்கணங்கள் இசைபாட
படைப்புகள் பாடம் சொல்ல
அதன் பரிசுகள் தாளம் போட
இனி ஆடுவோம் ஒரு தமிழாட்டம்..!"</item>

        <item>“கற்பனைத் தூரிகைப்பிடித்து- அதில்
தமிழினத்தின் வண்ணம் தோய்தது்த் தீடடி்டுவீர் ஓர் எழுத்தோவியம்...!!”</item>

        <item>“கருப்பு மைமீது காகிதம் கொண்ட காதலை
சிறப்பு மொழி கொண்டு நீ வார்க்கும் கவிதையை
வாழ்த்தி வரவேற்கிறது தமிழ்ச் சங்கத்தின் கவித்தோப்பு..!</item>

        <item>“படம்பிடிக்க வேண் டாம்,
படம் பிடித்தால் போதும்.
ரசிகரக் ளுக்கான மேடை இது..!”</item>

        <item>வைரமான வரிகள்
ரம்மியமான ராகங்கள்
தேன் சிந்தும் தாளங்கள்
பிடித்தாலே போதுமே மெட்டுப்போ ட..!</item>

        <item>“அமை தியை ஒலியாக்கி
அரங்கத்தின் ஒளியில்
மௌனத்தை மொழியாக்கி
சரித்திரம் படைக்க வாரீர்.!”</item>

        <item>“விதியல்ல, விளை யாடு! மதியோடு போராடு! வா! வெற்றி வாகை சூடு!
விஞ்ஞானமும் மெய்ஞானமும் எஞ்ஞானமும் உஞ்ஞானமாக !
நீதானே ராஜா ! எங்கள் ஆல் இன் ஆல் அழகுராஜா!!!”</item>

        <item>“சிரிப்பதோ எளிது
சிரிக்க வைப்பதோ அரிது
அறம்பட அவ்வரிய செயலைச்செய்ய திறம்பட வாரீர்.!</item>

        <item>“எழுத்தின் சக்தி, பாவத்தின் அழகு, இசையின் மயக்கம், இவையாவும் கலந்து, கதை சமைத்து,
பாத்திரம் உருத்து, தன்னிலை மறந்து, தன்னைத் தொலைத்து நவரசம் காட்டி மேடையை
ஆட்க்கொள்ள அனைவரையும் வரவேற்கிறது</item>

        <item>“பாத்திரத்தின் வடிவமாகும் நீர் போல கதாபாத்திரத்தைப் படிவங்கொண்டு நீர் தன்னந்தனியே
மகாராஜ்ஜியத்தை ஆட்டிப்படைக்க அழை க்கிறோம்..!”</item>

        <item>“நவரசம் கடைந்தெடுக்க இரசனையைத் தொகுத்து வசனத்தால் காவியம் படைக்க இனியதொரு தனி
நடையில் இணை ய வாருங்கள்..!”</item>

        <item>“மாறுதல்கள் செய்வதற்கோ மக்களை மகிழ்விப்பதற்கோ வாரத்தைகள் தேவையில்லை
இசைத் தோழனின் உதவியோடு உங்கள் எண்ணசசாரல்களை எங்கள் முன் சித்தரிக்க வாருங்கள்..!</item>

        <item>“முகம் மறைதது்
மௌனத்தில் சொல்லாடி
ரூப அரூபமுமாகி
நின்றேன் யாதுமாகி..!”</item>

        <item>வட்டார வழிகளிலே வற்றாத தமிழ் பேசி
அரசியலின் விழிகளிலே அறிவியல் கலை பூசி
அறிவு பெற்றாலும் புகழ் பண் பாட்டில்தான் - என
பாமரனும் சாமரம் வீசும் சாஸ் த்ராவின் கூத்துப்பட்டறை இது!”</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- tamil sangam rules list-->
    <string-array name="tamil_sangam_rules_list">

        <item>விதிமுறைகள் :
    • தனிநபர் பேச்சுப்போட்டி.
    • போட்டிக்கானத் தலைப்பு போட்டி நாளன்று தரப்படும்.
    • முதல் சுற்று தனிப்பேச்சாகவும் இரண்டாம் சுற்று கருத்தரங்கு வடிவிலும் அமையும்.
    • வன்மமும் ஈனதன்மையும் இல்லாதிருக்க வேண்டும்.
    • பிறமொழி கலவாத எளிய தமிழ் நடை போதுமானது.
    • நடுவரின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள் :
    • அணியாகப் பங்கேற்கும் தமிழ்ப் போட்டி.
    • அணிக்கு இருவர்.
    • தகுதிச்சுற்று தமிழ் சார்ந்த பொது வினாக்கள் கொண்ட எழுத்துச்சுற்று.
    • இறுதிச்சுற்று வினாடி வினா வடிவில் அமையும்.
    • நடுவரின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item> விதிமுறைகள் :
    • தனி நபர் பங்கேற்கும் போட்டி.
    • எழுதும் கதை சொந்தப் படைப்பாக இருத்தல் அவசியம்.
    • கதை நயம், கற்பனைத் திறன், தமிழ் ஆளுமை – இவற்றைச் சார்ந்து ஒரே சுற்றாய் அமைந்திருக்கும்.
    • சூழல்/தலைப்பு போட்டி நாளன்று வழங்கப்படும்.
    • நடுவரின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item> விதிமுறைகள் :
    • போட்டி நாளன்று தலைப்புகள் கொடுக்கப்படும்.
    • படைப்பின் தாக்கம், நடை, அமைப்பு ஆகியவை மதிப்பிடப்படும்.
    • நடுவர்களின் முடிவே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள் :
    • அணிக்கு மூவர்.
    • தகுதிச்சுற்றில் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கப்படும் அணிகள் மட்டும் இறுதி போட்டியில் பங்கேற்க அனுமதி.
    • பிறமொழி படங்கள் மற்றும் மொழி மாற்றம் செய்த படங்களில் இருந்து கேள்விகள் கேட்கப்படமாட்டாது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள் :
    • அணிக்கு மூவர்.
    • தகுதிச்சுற்றில் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கப்படும் அணிகள் மட்டும் இறுதி போட்டியில் பங்கேற்க அனுமதி.
    • தமிழ் சினிமாவில் இடம்பெற்றப் பாடல்களில் இருந்து மட்டுமே கேள்விகள் கேட்கப்படும்.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள் :
    • அணிக்கு மூவர்.
    • தகுதி சுற்றில் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கப்படும் அணிகள் மட்டுமே இறுதிப் போட்டியில் கலந்து கொள்ள அனுமதிக்கப்படுவார்கள்.
    • நடிப்பவர்கள் வாய் அசைத்தல் கூடாது.
    • வார்த்தைகளை அர்த்தம் இல்லாமல் பிரித்தல் கூடாது.
    • நடுவரின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள் :
    • அணிக்கு மூவர்.
    • தகுதிச்சுற்றில் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கப்படும் அணிகளே இறுதிச்சுற்றுக்கு அனுமதிக்கப்படுவார்கள் .
    • சினிமா,தமிழ்,பொது அறிவு,பேச்சுத்திறன் அனைத்தும் சோதிக்கப்படும்.
    • நடுவரின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது .</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள்:
    • அணிக்கு இருவர் மட்டும்.
    • நகைச்சுவையில் ஆபாசம் இருத்தல் கூடாது.(No vulgarity.No profanity)
    • போட்டியின் சுற்றுகள்:

முதல் சுற்று

பங்கேற்பாளரின் விருப்பம் (Either Mimicry,Stand-up,Variety)
கொடுக்கப்படும் அவகாசம்:  5 நிமிடங்கள்.

இரண்டாம் சுற்று

ஒலி மாற்று நகைச்சுவை (Video Spoof)

போட்டியின் விரிவாக்கம்:

முதலில் தகுதிச் சுற்று நடைபெறும். அதில் பங்கேற்பாளர்கள் அவர்கள் விருப்பத்திற்கு ஏற்ப நகைச்சுவைத் திறனை வெளிப்படுத்த வேண்டும்(Either mimicry, stand-up, variety or video spoof). அதில் தகுதி பெறுபவர்கள் இறுதிச் சுற்றில் பங்கேற்கலாம்.

இறுதிச் சுற்றின் இரண்டாவது சுற்றுக்கான ஒளித்துணுக்கு(video) போட்டிக்கு ஒரு நாள் முன் தரப்படும்.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள்:
    • குழுவில் நடிப்பு, இசை மற்றும் மேடை அமைப்பிற்கான உதவியாளர்கள் உட்பட மொத்தம் 12 நபர் வரை இருக்கலாம்.
    • திரையிசை அல்லாத பதிவுசெய்யப்பட்ட அல்லது வாத்திய இசையைப் பயன்படுத்தலாம்.
    • மேடை அமைப்பிற்கான நேரம் உட்பட மொத்தம் 25 நிமிடங்கள் மட்டுமே அளிக்கப்படும்.
    • அதிகமாக எடுத்துக்கொள்ளப்படும் ஒவ்வொரு நிமிடத்திற்கும் மதிப்பெண்கள் குறைக்கப்படும்.
    • குழுக்கள் தங்கள் நாடகத்தை விளம்பரப்படுத்த சுவரொட்டிகள் கொண்டுவரலாம்.
    • நெருப்பு, தண்ணீர் மற்றும் எவ்வகை திறவங்களையும் பயன்படுத்தக்கூடாது.
    • தமிழல்லாத பிற மொழிகள் 10% மேல் உபயோகிக்கக் கூடாது.
    • வன்மமும், ஈனத்தன்மையும் முற்றிலுமாகத் தவிர்க்கப்பட வேண்டும்.
    • தங்களின்  கதைவசனத்தை (script) 12/03/2019 ஆம் தேதிக்குள்   ststamizhsangam@gmail.com என்ற மின்னஞ்சல் முகவரிக்கு அனுப்பவும்.
    • நடுவர்களின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள்:
    • கால அவகாசம்: 6-8 நிமிடங்கள்
    • தனி மொழியாக இருக்கலாம் அல்லது தனி நடிப்பாக இருக்கலாம்.( Monologue or Monoact)
    • ஆபாச மொழியோ கொச்சைப் படுத்தும்படியான சொற்களையோ பயன்படுத்தக் கூடாது.
    • தமிழைத் தவிர்த்து பிற மொழிகளை 10 % மேல் உபயோகிக்காமல் இருக்கவேண்டும்.
    • மேடையிலிருந்து  நீங்கள் உபயோகித்த பொருட்களையெல்லாம் இறக்கிவிடவேண்டும்.
    • பின்னணி இசையோ இசைக்கருவிகளோ பயன் படுத்தக்கூடாது.
    • நெருப்பு, தண்ணீர் மற்றும் எவ்வகை திறவங்களையும் பயன்படுத்தக்கூடாது.
    • எவ்வகை இசையும் தவிர்க்கப்பட வேண்டும்.
    • நடுவர்களின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள்:
    • உங்கள் நாடகம் 25 நிமிடங்களுக்குள் முடியுமாறு இருத்தல் வேண்டும்(30 பக்கங்களுக்குள் எழுதுவது சிறந்தது).
    • அதிகபட்சமாக 10 கதாப்பாத்திரங்களை மட்டுமே கதைவசனம் கொண்டிருக்க வேண்டும்.
    • ஆபாச மொழியோ கொச்சைப் படுத்தும்படியான சொற்களையோ பயன்படுத்தக் கூடாது.
    • தமிழைத் தவிர்த்து பிற மொழிகளைப் 10 % மேல் உபயோகிக்கக் கூடாது.
    • உங்கள் கதைவசனத்தை ststamizhsangam@gmail.com  என்ற மின்னஞ்சல் முகவரிக்கோ அல்லது நேரிலோ 22/03/2019 அன்று கொடுக்கலாம்.
    • நடுவரின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள் :
    • ஓர் அணிக்கு 6 - 8 நபர்கள் இருக்கலாம்.
    • அணிக்கு 6-8 மணித்துளிகள் கொடுக்கப்படும்.
    • இசை, பதிவு செய்யப்பட்டதாகவோ வாத்திய இசையாகவோ இருக்கலாம்.
    • அணியினர் அனைவரும் ஒரே விதமான உடை மற்றும் முகச்சாயத்தில் இருக்க வேண்டும்.
    • அணியின் முகச்சாயல் முகமொழியின் மையக்கருத்தை வெளிப்படுத்தா வண்ணம் அமைதல் வேண்டும்.
    • அணியினர் அனைவரும் கையுறைகளும் காலுறைகளும் அணிந்திருக்க வேண்டும்.
    • சிறப்புப் பொருட்களை மேடையில் பயன்படுத்த அனுமதி இல்லை.
    • விளக்கப் படங்கள் பயன்படுத்தக் கூடாது.
    • எவ்விதக் குரல் ஒலியையும் பயன்படுத்த அனுமதி இல்லை.
    • அவைக்குப் பொருந்தாத செய்கைகள் கட்டாயமாகத் தவிர்க்கப்பட வேண்டும்.
    • நடுவர்களின் முடிவே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள்:
    • தனி நபர் பங்கேற்கும் போட்டி.
    • தகுதிச்சுற்றுக்கு 2 நிமிடங்கள் வழங்கப்படும்.
    • இரு பகுதிகளாகத் தகுதிச்சுற்று அமையும்.
    • முதல் பகுதியில் போட்டியளர்கள் தாம் தயார் செய்த நாடகத்தை நடித்துக் காட்ட வேண்டும்.
    • இரண்டாம் பகுதி பற்றிய விவரம் நிகழ்விடத்தில் அறிவுறுத்தப்படும்.
    • தகுதிச்சுற்றின் மூலம் போட்டியாளர்கள் தேர்வுசெய்யப்படுவார்கள்.
    • விளக்கப் படங்கள் பயன்படுத்தக்கூடாது.
    • குரலொலி கலவாத இசையைப் பயன்படுத்த மட்டுமே அனுமதி உண்டு.
    • சீரான உடை, முகச்சாயம், கையுறை, காலுறை அணிந்திருத்தல் அவசியம்.
    • அவைக்குப் பொருந்தாதச் செய்கைகள் ஏற்றுக்கொள்ளப்படமாட்டா.
    • நடுவரின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>

        <item>விதிமுறைகள்:
    • ஒவ்வொரு அணிக்கும் தலா 15 நிமிடங்கள் வழங்கப்படும்.
    • அணிக்கு குறைந்தது 9 முதல் அதிகபட்சமாக 12 நபர் வரை இருக்கலாம்.
    • மின் இசைக்கருவிகள் அனுமதிக்கப்படமாட்டாது.
    • திரைப்படப் பாடல் சாயலில் கூத்துப்பாடல் இருப்பதைத் தவிர்க்கவும்.
    • கருத்தின் தெளிவு, சமுதாயப் பிரச்சனைகளுக்கானத் தீர்வு, அணியின் ஒத்தியக்கம், தனித்தன்மை, குழுவினரின் பங்களிப்பு போன்றவற்றின் அடிப்படையில் தீர்ப்பு அமையும்.
    • அணியினர் அனைவரும் ஒரே விதமான உடையில் இருக்க வேண்டும் - தேவைப்பட்டால், கதை சொல்பவர்/ காட்சியை வழி நடத்திச் செல்பவர் வேறு உடை அணியலாம்.
    • வன்மமும், ஈனத்தன்மையும் முற்றிலுமாகத் தவிர்க்கப்பட வேண்டும்.
    • தண்ணீர் மற்றும் நெருப்பு மேடையில் பயன்படுத்தக் கூடாது.
    • நடுவர்களின் தீர்ப்பே இறுதியானது.</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--music team events list-->
    <string-array name="music_team_list">
        <item>Eastern band event- Synchrotune</item>
        <item>KS Idol</item>
        <item>Carnatic Solo Vocal</item>
        <item>Western solo vocal</item>
        <item>Instrumental: eastern</item>
        <item>instrumental: western</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- music team desc list-->
    <string-array name="music_team_desc_list">
        <item>BE PREPARED TO BE TRANSPORTED TO EVERY NOOK AND CORNER OF THE MAJESTIC COUNTRY THAT IS
INDIA. SHOWCASE YOUR EXHILARATING AND STAGE-ROCKING MUSIC AT THE EASTERN BAND EVENT.
EXPLORE THE COLOURFUL HARMONIC CAVES OF THE NATION AND TAKE YOUR AUDIENCE ON A TRIP,
QUITE LITERALLY. PACK YOUR BAGS, GRAB YOUR INSTRUMENTS AND GET READY FOR THE MUSICAL
‘ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME’.</item>

        <item>MUSIC TRANSCENDS BOUNDARIES. HERE IS AN AVENUE TO EXHIBIT YOUR SINGING TALENT AND AN
OPPORTUNITY TO ENTHRAL THE AUDIENCE WITH YOUR MELLIFLUOUS SINGING. WE PRESENT TO YOU KS
IDOL, THE STAGE THAT WILL WITNESS ASPIRING SINGERS SHOWCASING THEIR SINGING PROWESS TO WIN
THIS GLORIOUS TITLE.</item>

        <item>DEVOTION CAN BE ENJOYED, FELT AND REJOICED THROUGH MUSIC. WE WELCOME YOU TO PARTICIPATE
IN OUR EVENT TO CELEBRATE THE ENCHANTING RENDITIONS IN THIS RICH CULTURAL HERITAGE. LET’S
COME TOGETHER IN THE SPIRIT OF MUSIC!</item>

        <item>DO YOU THINK THAT YOU ARE THE NEXT ADELE, CHRIS MARTIN, RIHANNA OR JOHN MAyER?
DO YOU WANT TO BREAK AWAY FROM THE CROWD AND GO SOLO? LOOK NO FURTHER! THIS IS YOUR
TICKET TO TAKE US ACROSS THE GLOBE AND ENTHRAL US WITH THE MAGIC OF YOUR VOICE.</item>

        <item>TRAVEL ACROSS THE ETHNIC DIMENSIONS OF INDIAN MUSIC AND EXPERIENCE THE THRILL OF RAAGAS
AND DIFFERENT TAALAS. SHOW THE WORLD THAT YOU ARE INDEED THE TRUE MASTER OF YOUR
INSTRUMENT. WE INVITE ALL THE ASPIRING MUSICIANS OUT THERE TO EMBARK ON A JOURNEY AND TO
REDISCOVER EASTERN INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC.</item>

        <item>DO YOU THINK THAT YOU ARE THE NEXT CORY HENRY, MICHAEL LEAGUE OR MARK LETTIERI?
DO YOUR HANDS ITCH TO PLAY THE BEST SOLO THAT THIS WORLD HAS EVER HEARD? ITCH NO FURTHER.
PLUG IN YOUR INSTRUMENT AND BLOW OUR MINDS WITH AMAZING RIFFS AND DELICATE RUNS AT
KURUKSASTRA’S WESTERN INSTRUMENTAL EVENT.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- music team rules list-->
    <string-array name="music_team_rules_list">
        <item>• A BAND CAN HAVE A MAXIMUM OF 12 MEMBERS ON STAGE.\n
• EVERY BAND IS ALLOWED 18 MINUTES OF STAGE TIME INCUDING SETUP.\n
• A STANDARD 5 PIECE KIT, A KEYBOARD STAND AND AMPS WILL BE PROVIDED.\n
• THE USE OF ARPEGGIATORS AND PRE-RECORDED BEATS ARE NOT ALLOWED.\n
• OWN COMPOSITIONS WILL BE AWARDED EXTRA POINTS.\n
• BANDS WILL BE JUDGED BASED ON THEIR TIGHTNESS, CLARITY AND DYNAMICS.\n
• NO FORM OF VULGARITY WILL BE TOLERATED ON STAGE.</item>

        <item>• THE EVENT WILL CONSIST OF THREE ROUNDS.\n
• •PARTICIPANTS CAN PERFORM SONGS FROM ANY INDIAN MOVIE OR ALBUM IN THE FIRST ROUND. THE\n
PARTICIPANTS WILL BE INFORMED ABOUT THE OTHER TWO ROUNDS ON THE SPOT.\n
• ALL THE PARTICIPANTS ARE EXPECTED TO BE PREPARED WITH 3 OR 4 SONGS IN DIFFERENT GENRES.\n
• THE JUDGE’S DECISION WILL BE FINAL.\n
• EVENT REGISTRATION WILL BE DONE ON THE SPOT.\n
• PARTICIPANTS SHOULD HAVE A VALID COLLEGE ID.</item>

        <item>• PARTICIPANTS HAVE TO PERFORM A CARNATIC OR HINDUSTANI PIECE ONLY.\n
• EACH PARTICIPANT WILL BE GIVEN 5 MINUTES ON STAGE.\n
• ACCOMPANIMENTS ARE NOT ALLOWED.\n
• RAGAM, NERAVAL AND KALPANASWARAM WILL FETCH EXTRA POINTS.\n
• A SHRUTI BOX WILL BE PROVIDED DURING THE EVENT.\n
• THE JUDGE’S DECISION WILL BE FINAL.</item>

        <item>• PARTICIPANTS HAVE TO PERFORM SONGS IN ENGLISH ONLY.\n
• EACH PARTICIPANT WILL BE GIVEN 5 MINUTES ON STAGE.\n
• EITHER A KARAOKE TRACK OR ONE ACCOMPANYING INSTRUMENT IS ALLOWED.\n
• THE JUDGE’S DECISION WILL BE FINAL.</item>

        <item>• PARTICIPANTS HAVE TO PERFORM A CARNATIC, HINDUSTANI OR WESTERN PIECE ONLY.\n
• EACH PARTICIPANT IS GIVEN A TIME LIMIT Of 5 MINUTES ONSTAGE.\n
• THE JUDGE ‘S DECISION WILL BE FINAL.\n
• FILM SONGS PLAYED AS INSTRUMENTAL ARE STRICTLY NOT ALLOWED.\n
• A KEYBOARD STAND AND GUITAR AMPS WILL BE PROVIDED.</item>

        <item>• PARTICIPANTS HAVE TO PERFORM A CARNATIC, HINDUSTANI OR WESTERN PIECE ONLY.\n
• EACH PARTICIPANT IS GIVEN A TIME LIMIT Of 5 MINUTES ONSTAGE.\n
• THE JUDGE ‘S DECISION WILL BE FINAL.\n
• FILM SONGS PLAYED AS INSTRUMENTAL ARE STRICTLY NOT ALLOWED.\n
• A KEYBOARD STAND AND GUITAR AMPS WILL BE PROVIDED.</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- 300dpi events-->
    <string-array name="dpi_list">
        <item>The minimalist</item>
        <item>A-Dobe</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- 300 dpi desc list-->
    <string-array name="dpi_desc_list">
        <item>This is an online event focusing on the poster making skills.</item>
        <item>• Design a poster for The Indian dance festival held at Thanjavur,Tamilnadu from March
22 to 24 where notable exponents of the various Indian dance forms are performed.\n
• Design a poster for the 25th Street art festival where over 600 artists converge
to turn the streets of Chennai on March 22 at 6 pm into a temporary gallery of art,
creating a diverse variety of large scale traditional, contemporary and illusionist
paintings on the street.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- 300 dpi rules list-->
    <string-array name="dpi_rules_list">
        <item>• This is an online contest where Participants should design minimal movie posters on any
movie of their choice.\n
• The final jpeg image(should not exceed 5MB) and PSD file(should not exceed 50MB) has to be
mailed to 300dpi.ks@sastra.ac.in before 20th March\n
• Any sign of plagiarism may lead to disqualification.\n
• Profanity or vulgarity is strictly prohibited.\n
• The resolution should be set to 300DPI.\n
• Specify your name and college name in the mail body or heading.\n
• Software choice is not restricted.\n
• Only one entry is allowed per participant.</item>

        <item>• The final jpeg image(should not exceed 5 MB) and PSD file( should not exceed50MB) has to be
mailed to 300dpi.ks@sastra.ac.in.\n
• Specify the chosen prompt in the subject and participant’s name,college name in the mail
heading or mail body.\n
• Last day of submission is on or before 20th March after which entries will be eliminated.\n
• Any sign of plagiarism may lead to disqualification.\n
• Software choice is not restricted.\n
• The resolution should be set to 300DPI.\n
• Only one entry is allowed per participant.\n
• Winner is picked based on the creativity,originality and how much the given theme is
satisfied</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--About-->
    <string name="about_ks">If Kurukshetra was the greatest battle in Hindu mythology, Kuruksastra is the greatest battle of Southern India to establish proven talent and bring to the fore previously unheralded ones.<br /><br />
        A sublime melange of style and substance, glamour and colour, Kuruksastra, SASTRA\'s cultural bonanza consists of arts, music, literary events(English, Tamil and Hindi) and dance.<br /><br />
        Top Institutes from all over India turn up to give fierce competition to each other in the race to win the ultimate prize- the title of overall championship at Kuruksastra.<br /><br />
        The Pro show is the highlight of KS. Eminent artistes who can really set the stage on fire have been a permanent feature of our pro-nights.<br /><br /> Stars like Shankar Mahadevan, Benny Dayal, Crazy Mohan and Naresh Iyer,among others, have always left enthusiastic crowds asking for more.
        In a short span of 4 years, KS has shown phenomenal response and is only going to get bigger this year.<br /><br />With the student group and support staff we have and going by the response that the fest has received, there is no looking back.
        It offers unlimited opportunities to talented students who are given the limelight to enthral the buzzing crowds with mind blowing performances.<br /><br />Enough reason for all of you to turn up in numbers and show the world what you are made of!
    </string>

    <string name="about_sastra">The dreams of its founding fathers took shape in 1984 in the form of Shanmugha College of Engineering, which is now renamed, SHANMUGHA ARTS, SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY and RESEARCH ACADEMY (SASTRA).
        Our programmes, infrastructure, teaching-learning, etc., are among the country\'s finest.<br /><br />
        SASTRA has always been proactive in its academic planning and believes in gaining the first-mover advantage.<br /><br />
        As a testimony to this, the Government of India has conferred the Deemed University status to SASTRA on April 26, 2001 under section 3 of the UGC Act, 1956.<br /><br />
        SASTRA offers various undergraduate and post graduate courses in Engineering, Science, Education, Management, Law and Arts besides various Doctoral programmes and has state-of-the-art laboratories, a well stocked library and one of the best computing facilities.<br /><br />
        With a sprawling campus having a built-up area of 2,22,129.02 square metre spread over 232 acres and a vibrant population of over 10,000 students and over 700 teaching faculty have made SASTRA a landmark in the educational map of India.<br /><br />
        With an ideal teacher-taught ratio, we strive for academic excellence through personalized attention. The mechanisms established to support and monitor the student\’s progress assure success and satisfaction.<br /><br />
        Since its inception SASTRA has achieved national standing in terms of academic performance, co-curricular and extra-curricular activities and also in its growth and commitment to social service.<br /><br />
        The standards of excellence of our programmes are reflected in the grades awarded to us by the National Assessment and Accreditation Council and in the success of our students in industry and academia, both in India and abroad.<br /><br />
        SASTRA has also been re-accredited with Grade ‘A’ (maximum) by the National Accreditation and Assessment Council (NAAC) a statutory body of U.G.C.<br /><br />
        SASTRA shapes its students\' future by fostering a teamwork approach to instruction, encouraging interaction with faculty, providing access to high tech information, motivating them to develop new ideas and concepts, taking personal interest in students\' career development and preparing them for success.
    </string>

    <string name="about_uphar">Ever since the first edition of Kuruksastra, it has been getting more action packed and fun filled with assimilation of spanking new ideas. <br /><br />Kuruksastra XII promises not only these, but also a chance which can give you the happiness-contentment in the truest sense.<br /><br />
        Most of us have been lucky to get all that we have ever needed, good schooling, as many clothes as we want, and needless to say, food, healthy and nourishing.<br /><br /> But there are millions out there, who are not as fortunate as us, who do not have these amenities, which are the primary requisites of life. <br /><br />For them, our most humble contribution can ameliorate their lives.
        KS Uphaar is an earnest initiative to raise funds that can directly be utilized in providing education essentials in schools in and around Trichy and Thanjavur.<br /><br />
        Kuruksastra Upahaar team has envisaged accomplishing this non-profit fundraising by having collection boxes in all the clusters and other popular hangouts in the campus. <br /><br />The idea behind this fund-raising is to let the poor and needy children gain something useful when we have fun. <br /><br />Hence, the team has decided to conduct a few fun events and the money collected will be slided to KSU.<br /><br /> The contribution, how much ever modest can be made, with a complete idea of how every penny of it is eventually going to be put to use.<br /><br />
        If foregoing a burger or cold coffee can bring a smile on a thousand faces, is it not worth it?<br /><br /> As they say, children are our future, let us be a small ray of hope in the beam of light that they need to establish a bright tomorrow. Join KS Upahaar!!

    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>
